Finding Aid for the Music Department Photograph Collection, circa 1920-2008
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
Music Department Photograph Collection, circa 1920-2008
Mus. Arc. 16
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
9 boxes (639 items)
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library 112 Baird Hall Buffalo, New York 14260-4750 United States Phone: 716 645-2924 Fax: 716 645-3906
The images in the collection provide documentation of performances at the University at Buffalo by Music Dept. faculty and visiting artists, especially in the realm of contemporary music. Among the many notable composers represented in the collection are: Earle Brown, Harrison Birtwistle, Pauline Oliveros, Colin Bright, Julius Eastman, John Cage, Morton Feldman, Lejaren Hiller, Cornelius Cardew, Carlos Chavez, Aaron Copland, Lukas Foss, Elliott Carter, David Del Tredici, Harold Shapero, Ralph Shapey, Ingolf Dahl, Henri Pousseur, Philip Glass, George Crumb, Fredric Myrow, Leon Kirchner, George Rochberg, New Rorem, Allen Sapp, Toru Takemitsu, Morton Subotnick, Leo Smit, and Augusta Read Thomas.
Administrative Information
Terms of Access
Materials can be examined by qualified researchers in the Music Library during hours of operation during which Music Librarians are present. In order to insure access, researchers are advised to contact the Music Library in advance of visits.
Acquisition Information
Materials acquired by the Music Library from the Music Department and the Center for the Creative and Performing Arts since 1968.
Accruals and Additions
Additional accruals possible on irregular basis.
Alternate Forms
Collection has been digitized and is available in University Libraries Digital Collections.
Historical Note
The Music Department of the University at Buffalo truly began to flourish in the late 1950s and early 1960s. With the establishment of the Center of the Creative and Performing Arts in 1964, the Music Department became a major international location for the performance and composition of new music. The Center awarded positions to musicians to come to Buffalo and become Creative Associates of the Center. The Center, including participation by the Creative Associates, Univeristy at Buffalo Music Department faculty, and the many visiting musicians who came to Buffalo, was chiefly responsible for Buffalo's reputation during the 1960s and 1970s for being very hospitable to whatever was new in the arts.
The Department also benefited from two projects funded by local businessman and amateur musician, Frederick Slee: the Slee Beethoven String Quartet Cycle series and the Slee Visiting Professors in Music Theory and Composition. The performances of the Beethoven quartet cycle began in 1955 with performances by the Budapest Quartet and continues to this day. The Slee Professorship attracted several of the most noted composers of the period, including Aaron Copland, Carlos Chavez, David Diamond, Leo Smit, George Rochberg, Ned Rorem, Harrison Birtwistle, Mauricio Kagel, Henri Pousseur, Morton Feldman, Leon Kirchner, and Lejaren Hiller.
Scope and Content Note
The Music Department Photograph Collection contains 639 photographs of musicians who have participated in events of the Music Deptartment dating back to ca. 1920. This includes music faculty, students (though not student events and ensembles), and visiting musicians. The collection is especially strong in its representations of performers and composers of contemporary music from 1960-2000. Many of these musicians came to Buffalo as visiting faculty or as Creative Associates at the Center of the Creative and Performing Arts (1964-1980). The list of composers in the collection is impressive. It includes: Earle Brown, Harrison Birtwistle, Pauline Oliveros, Colin Bright, Julius Eastman, John Cage, Morton Feldman, Lejaren Hiller, Cornelius Cardew, Carlos Chavez, Aaron Copland, Lukas Foss, Elliott Carter, David Del Tredici, Harold Shapero, Mauricio Kagel, Ralph Shapey, Ingolf Dahl, Henri Pousseur, Philip Glass, George Crumb, Fredric Myrow, Leon Kirchner, George Rochberg, New Rorem, Allen Sapp, Toru Takemitsu, Morton Subotnick, Leo Smit, and Augusta Read Thomas.
The Music Department at the University at Buffalo has also hosted more than 24 string quartets that have performed the Slee Beethoven String Quartet Cycle series dating back to 1955. The collection includes photographs of the Budapest, Cassatt, Cleveland, Colorado, Concord, Emerson, Guarnieri, Juilliard, Orford, Prague, and Vermeer string quartets.
Arrangement
The collection is in one series arranged alphabetically by the principal subject. Newly acquired images are placed at the end of the collection.
Container List
- Photographs, circa 1920-2008, I.
  - Pamela Benjamin Adelstein (Pamela McConnell), violist, December 31, 1986, 1 black and white photograph; Nowak, Edward L. (Box 1, Item MD01-001)
  - Pamela Benjamin Adelstein (McConnell), violist, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item MD01-002)
  - Maryanne Amacher, composer at console, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Osterreicher, Mickey (Box 1, Item MD01-003)
  - Michael Andriaccio, guitarist standing, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item MD01-004)
  - Artpark Theatre, concert, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item MD01-005)
  - Artpark Theatre, aerial view, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item MD01-006)
  - Artpark, Amphitheatre, June 1975, 1 black and white photograph; Rusiniak, Chris (Box 1, Item MD01-007)
  - Artpark, Amphitheatre, June 1975, 1 black and white photograph; Rusiniak, Chris (Box 1, Item MD01-008)
  - Artpark (contact sheet), with images of Julius Eastman, 1975, 1 black and white contact sheet; Rusiniak, Chris (Box 1, Item MD01-009)
  - Robert Ashley and Walter Gajewski, composers at console, December 1975, 1 black and white photograph; J & J Prods (Buffalo) (Box 1, Item MD01-010)
  - Robert Ashley, Walter Gajewski, and Linda Cummiskey, musicians on stage, December 1975, 1 black and white photograph; J & J Prods (Buffalo) (Box 1, Item MD01-011)
  - Edward P. Asmus, faculty, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item MD01-012)
  - Cameron Baird, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item MD01-013)
  - University at Buffalo North Campus buildings: Baird, Clemens, and Slee Hall, 1981, 1 black and white photograph; Nowak, Edward L. (Box 1, Item MD01-014)
  - Lee Bash directing the UB Jazz Ensemble, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Christopher, Phyllis (Box 1, Item MD01-015)
  - John Bergamo, percussionist, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Sinderbrand (Box 1, Item MD01-016)
  - Michael von Biel, composer, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item MD01-017)
  - Harrison Birtwistle, composer, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item MD01-018)
  - Frina Boldt, piano, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Willoughby, Robert (Box 1, Item MD01-019)
  - Stephen Bradley, audio technician, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item MD01-020)
  - Stephen Bradley, audio technician, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item MD01-021)
  - Colin Bright, composer with percussionists, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item MD01-022)
  - Colin Bright, composer with percussionists, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item MD01-023)
  - Earle Brown, composer conducting, 1978, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item MD01-024)
  - Earle Brown, composer conducting, 1978, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item MD01-025)
  - Earle Brown, composer conducting, 1978, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item MD01-026)
  - Earle Brown, composer, conducting, 1978, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item MD01-027)
  - Earle Brown, composer, conducting ensemble onstage, February 1978, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item MD01-028)
  - Earle Brown, composer, conducting ensemble ontsage, February 1978, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item MD01-029)
  - Earle Brown, composer, conducting ensemble onstage, February 1978, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item MD01-030)
  - Earle Brown, composer, conducting ensemble onstage, February 1978, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item MD01-031)
  - Earle Brown, composer, conducting ensemble onstage, February 1978, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item MD01-032)
  - Earle Brown, composer, conducting ensemble onstage, February 1978, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item MD01-033)
  - Earle Brown, composer, conducting ensemble onstage, February 1978, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item MD01-034)
  - Earle Brown, composer, conducting ensemble onstage, February 1978, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item MD01-035)
  - Earle Brown, composer, conducting ensemble onstage, February 1978, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item MD01-036)
  - Earle Brown, composer with musicians, including Morton Feldman, Jan Williams, Eberhard Blum, and other Creative Associates (contact sheet), June 2 1978, 1 black and white photograph; Nowak, Edward L. (Box 1, Item MD01-037)
  - Budapest String Quartet, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item MD01-038)
  - Gary Burgess, vocalist, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item MD01-039)
  - Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra rehearsing, November 19 1981, 1 black and white photograph; Nowak, Edward L. (Box 1, Item MD01-040)
  - Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra performing, 1966-1967, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item MD01-041)
  - Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra performing, November 19 1981, 1 black and white photograph; Nowak, Edward L. (Box 1, Item MD01-042)
  - Edward Burnham, percussionist, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 1, Item MD01-043)
  - Edward Burnham, percussionist, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item MD01-044)
  - John Cage, composer being appluaded, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Kiessling, Hermann (Berlin) (Box 1, Item MD01-045)
  - John Cage, composer at piano, March 1968, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 1, Item MD01-046)
  - John Cage, composer at piano, March 1968, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 1, Item MD01-047)
  - John Cage, composer at piano, March 1968, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 1, Item MD01-048)
  - John Cage with toy gun during performance of David Rosenboom's To That Predestined Dancing Place at Albright-Knox Art Gallery performance for the 2nd Festival of the Arts, March 1968, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 1, Item MD01-049)
  - John Cage, composer seated in audience, with Morton Feldman in some shots (contact sheet), June 2 1978, 1 black and white contact sheet; Nowak, Edward L. (Box 1, Item MD01-050)
  - Cornelius Cardew, composer onstage, April 29 1967, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 1, Item MD01-051)
  - Elliott Carter with Lejaren Hiller, Morton Feldman, and George R. Levine, October 14 1979, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item MD01-052)
  - Elliott Carter with Lejaren Hiller, Morton Feldman, and George R. Levine, October 14 1979, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item MD01-053)
  - Cassatt String Quartet, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Hunstein, Don (Box 1, Item MD01-054)
  - Cassatt String Quartet, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Hunstein, Don (Box 1, Item MD01-055)
  - Joanne Castellani, guitarist, 1986, 1 black and white photograph; Bush, Jim (Box 1, Item MD01-056)
  - Carlos Chávez, composer, 1952, 1 black and white photograph; Foto-Semo (Mexico) (Box 1, Item MD01-057)
  - Amrom Chodos, clarinetist, September 23 1973, 1 black and white photograph; Osterreicher, Mickey (Box 1, Item MD01-058)
  - Amrom Chodos, clarinetist, September 23 1973, 1 black and white photograph; Osterreicher, Mickey (Box 1, Item MD01-059)
  - Frank Cipolla, conductor, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item MD01-060)
  - Frank Cipolla, conductor, with UB Symphonic Wind Ensemble and trumpet soloist, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item MD01-061)
  - Frank Cipolla, conductor, with UB Symphonic Wind Ensemble, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item MD01-062)
  - Frank Cipolla, conductor, with UB Symphonic Wind Ensemble, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item MD01-063)
  - Frank Cipolla, conductor, with UB Symphonic Wind Ensemble, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item MD01-064)
  - Frank Cipolla, conductor, with UB Symphonic Wind Ensemble, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item MD01-065)
  - Frank Cipolla, conductor, with UB Symphonic Wind Ensemble, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item MD01-066)
  - Cleveland Quartet, November 20 1986, 1 black and white photograph; Schaaf, Peter (Box 2, Item MD02-001)
  - Cleveland Quartet, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item MD02-002)
  - Cleveland Quartet, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Salaff, Fred (Box 2, Item MD02-003)
  - Colorado Quartet, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Sever, Peter J (Box 2, Item MD02-004)
  - Colorado Quartet, 1985, 1 black and white photograph; Schaaf, Peter (Box 2, Item MD02-005)
  - Douglas Cone, violinist, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item MD02-006)
  - Concord String Quartet, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Briggs, Eleanor (Box 2, Item MD02-007)
  - Concord String Quartet, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Briggs, Eleanor (Box 2, Item MD02-008)
  - Judith Coon playing recorder, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item MD02-009)
  - Aaron Copland, composer with Morton Feldman and Leo Smit, June 1 1977, 1 black and white photograph; Nowak, Edward L. (Box 2, Item MD02-010)
  - Aaron Copland, composer, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Boosey & Hawkes (Box 2, Item MD02-011)
  - Aaron Copland, composer conducting, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item MD02-012)
  - Creative Associates (State University of New York at Buffalo), Fall 1967, 1 black and white photograph; Glena, Don (Box 2, Item MD02-013)
  - Creative Associates (State University of New York at Buffalo), Fall 1970, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 2, Item MD02-014)
  - Creative Associates (State University of New York at Buffalo), Fall 1970, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 2, Item MD02-015)
  - Creative Associates (State University of New York at Buffalo), Fall 1970, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 2, Item MD02-016)
  - Creative Associates (State University of New York at Buffalo), Fall 1970, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 2, Item MD02-017)
  - Creative Associates (State University of New York at Buffalo), Fall 1970, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 2, Item MD02-018)
  - Creative Associates (State University of New York at Buffalo), 1973, September 23 1973, 1 black and white photograph; Osterreicher, Mickey (Box 2, Item MD02-019)
  - Creative Associates (State University of New York at Buffalo), 1973, September 23 1973, 1 black and white photograph; Osterreicher, Mickey (Box 2, Item MD02-020)
  - Creative Associates (State University of New York at Buffalo), Fall 1974, 1974, 1 black and white photograph; Osterreicher, Mickey (Box 2, Item MD02-021)
  - Creative Associates (State University of New York at Buffalo), Fall 1974, 1 black and white photograph; Osterreicher, Mickey (Box 2, Item MD02-022)
  - Creative Associates (State University of New York at Buffalo), Fall 1975, 1 black and white photograph; J & J Prods (Buffalo) (Box 2, Item MD02-023)
  - Creative Associates (State University of New York at Buffalo), Fall 1975, 1 black and white photograph; J & J Prods (Buffalo) (Box 2, Item MD02-024)
  - Creative Associates (State University of New York at Buffalo), Fall 1975, 1 black and white photograph; J & J Prods (Buffalo) (Box 2, Item MD02-025)
  - Creative Associates (State University of New York at Buffalo), Fall 1975, 1 black and white photograph; J & J Prods (Buffalo) (Box 2, Item MD02-026)
  - Creative Associates (State University of New York at Buffalo), January 1974, 1 black and white photograph; Bratesman, Stuart (Box 2, Item MD02-027)
  - Creative Associates (State University of New York at Buffalo), January 1974, 1 black and white photograph; Bratesman, Stuart (Box 2, Item MD02-028)
  - Creative Associates (State University of New York at Buffalo) (contact sheet), January 1974, 1 black and white contact sheet; Bratesman, Stuart (Box 2, Item MD02-029)
  - Creative Associates (State University of New York at Buffalo), Fall 1977, 1 black and white photograph; Seman, David (Box 2, Item MD02-030)
  - Creative Associates (State University of New York at Buffalo), undated, 1 black and white photograph; Osterreicher, Mickey (Box 2, Item MD02-031)
  - Creative Associates (State University of New York at Buffalo) (contact sheet), Fall 1975, 1 black and white contact sheet; J & J Prods (Buffalo) (Box 2, Item MD02-032)
  - George Crumb, composer outdoors, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Matthes, Sabine (Box 2, Item MD02-033)
  - George Crumb, composer at piano, 1965, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item MD02-034)
  - George Crumb, composer at piano, 1965, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item MD02-035)
  - George Crumb, composer at piano, 1965, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item MD02-036)
  - George Crumb, composer with Buell Neidlinger, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Sinderbrand (Box 2, Item MD02-037)
  - George Crumb, composer with competition winners, undated, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item MD02-038)
  - Linda Cummiskey, violinist, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Osterreicher, Mickey (Box 2, Item MD02-039)
  - Linda Cummiskey, violinist, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Osterreicher, Mickey (Box 2, Item MD02-040)
  - Linda Cummiskey, violinist, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Osterreicher, Mickey (Box 2, Item MD02-041)
  - Linda Cummiskey, violinist, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Osterreicher, Mickey (Box 2, Item MD02-042)
  - Douglas Davis, violoncellist with Howard Zwickler in background, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Parman, Frank (Box 2, Item MD02-043)
  - Douglas Davis, violoncellist, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Parman, Frank (Box 2, Item MD02-044)
  - Douglas Davis, violoncellist, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Parman, Frank (Box 2, Item MD02-045)
  - Douglas Davis, violoncellist with Roger Shields at piano, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 2, Item MD02-046)
  - David Del Tredici, composer leaning on piano, Fall 1972, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item MD02-047)
  - David Del Tredici, composer, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mitchell, Jack (Box 2, Item MD02-048)
  - Stuart Dempster, trombonist, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 2, Item MD02-049)
  - Stuart Dempster, trombonist, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 2, Item MD02-050)
  - Stuart Dempster, trombonist, March 10 1968, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 2, Item MD02-051)
  - Robert Dick, flutist (contact sheet), undated, 1 black and white contact sheet; Unidentified (Box 2, Item MD02-052)
  - Robert Dick, flutist (contact sheet), undated, 1 black and white contact sheet; Unidentified (Box 2, Item MD02-053)
  - Sylvia Dimiziani, vocalist, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Ecofotografico (Rome) (Box 2, Item MD02-054)
  - Sylvia Dimiziani, vocalist, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Ecofotografico (Rome) (Box 2, Item MD02-055)
  - Sylvia Dimiziani, vocalist, 1972, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 2, Item MD02-056)
  - Sylvia Dimiziani, vocalist, 1972, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 2, Item MD02-057)
  - Dean Drummond, composer in rehearsal, March 19 1978, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item MD02-058)
  - Richard Dufallo, conductor, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item MD02-059)
  - Richard Dufallo, conductor, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item MD02-060)
  - Richard Dufallo, conductor with Creative Associates (rehearsal), March 19 1967, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 2, Item MD02-061)
  - Richard Dufallo, conductor with Creative Associates (performance), March 19 1967, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 2, Item MD02-062)
  - Richard Dufallo, conductor with Creative Associates (rehearsal), March 19 1967, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 2, Item MD02-063)
  - Richard Dufallo, conductor with Creative Associates (rehearsal), March 19 1967, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 2, Item MD02-064)
  - Richard Dufallo, conductor with Creative Associates (rehearsal), March 19 1967, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 2, Item MD02-065)
  - Richard Dufallo, conductor with Creative Associates (rehearsal), March 19 1967, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 2, Item MD02-066)
  - Joseph Dunn, Creative Associate with Frank Parman, 1970-1971, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item MD02-067)
  - Jean Dupouy, violist playing, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item MD02-068)
  - Jean Dupouy, violist in rest position, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item MD02-069)
  - Julius Eastman, composer with Lukas Foss and Douglas Davis on stage, November 1970, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 2, Item MD02-070)
  - Julius Eastman, composer/vocalist, rehearsing Peter Maxwell Davies' Eight Songs for A Mad King, November 1 1970, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 2, Item MD02-071)
  - Julius Eastman, composer/vocalist, rehearsing Peter Maxwell Davies' Eight Songs for a Mad King, November 1 1970, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 2, Item MD02-072)
  - Julius Eastman, composer/vocalist rehearsing Peter Maxwell Davies' Eight Songs for a Mad King, November 1 1970, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 2, Item MD02-073)
  - Julius Eastman, composer/vocalist rehearsing Peter Maxwell Davies' Eight Songs for a Mad King, November 1 1970, 1 black and white photograph; Tuttle, Jim (Box 2, Item MD02-074)
  - Julius Eastman, composer/vocalist performing Peter Maxwell Davies' Eight Songs for a Mad King, November 1 1970, 1 black and white photograph; Osterreicher, Mickey (Box 2, Item MD02-075)
  - Julius Eastman, composer/vocalist performing Peter Maxwell Davies' Eight Songs for a Mad King, November 1 1970, 1 black and white photograph; Greenberg-May Prod. (Buffalo) (Box 2, Item MD02-076)
  - Julius Eastman, composer/vocalist performing Peter Maxwell Davies' Eight Songs for a Mad King, 1975, 1 black and white photograph; Rusiniak, Chris (Box 2, Item MD02-077)
  - Julius Eastman, composer/vocalist rehearsing Peter Maxwell Davies' Eight Songs for a Mad King, 1975, 1 black and white photograph; Osterreicher, Mickey (Box 2, Item MD02-078)
  - Julius Eastman, composer/vocalist rehearsing Peter Maxwell Davies' Eight Songs for a Mad King, 1975, 1 black and white photograph; Osterreicher, Mickey (Box 2, Item MD02-079)